let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "Which array method removes an element from the end of the array list?",
    answer: "C. .pop",
    options: ["A. .push", "B. .remove", "C. .pop", "D. .shift"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How do you remove an element from an array at a specific index?",
    answer: "A. using array.splice method",
    options: [
      "A. using array.splice method",
      "B. using array.shift method",
      "C. using array.filter method",
      "D. using array.reduce method",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the difference between .map() and .forEach()",
    answer: "B. map() returns a new array while .forEach() does not return a new array",
    options: [
      "A. map() does not return a new array while forEach() returns a new array",
      "B. map() returns a new array while .forEach() does not return a new array",
      "C. .map() is mutable while forEach is immutable",
      "D. All of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is not an array method?",
    answer: "D. toString()",
    options: [
      "A. .reduce()",
      "B. findIndex()",
      "C. .map()",
      "D. toString()",
    ],
  },
  // {
  //   numb: 5,
  //   question: "Which of the following is not true about .every() array method?",
  //   answer:
  //     "C. returns false if one of the array elements fails the function test",
  //   options: [
  //     "A. returns true if one of the array elements passes the function test",
  //     "B. returns true if all of the array element fails the function test",
  //     "C. returns false if one of the array element fails the function test ",
  //     "D. returns the all the elements of the array ",
  //   ],
  // },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following Date() method is not ideal to use.",
    answer: "A. getYear()",
    options: ["A. getYear()", "B. getMonth()", "C. getFullYear()", "D. None of the above."],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "what does this method returns new Date(2023-10-23).getMonth()?",
    answer: "B. 9",
    options: ["A. October", "B. 9", "C. September", "10."],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question:
      "Which of the following is not a valid Date() method?",
    answer: "C. toTUCString()",
    options: ["A. toISOString()", "B. getMinutes()", "C. toTUCString()", "D. toUTCString()"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question:
      "Which CSS property is used to specify uppercase and lowercase letters in a text?",
    answer: "C. text-transform",
    options: ["A. text-case", "B. case", "C. text-transform", "D. text-casing"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Can we hide content using the comment?",
    answer: "B. YES",
    options: ["A. NO", "B. YES", "C. NOT SURE", "D. E BE LIKE SO"],
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "In how many ways can CSS be written in?",
    answer: "C. 3",
    options: ["A. 1", "B. 2", "C. 3", "D. 4"],
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question:
      "What type of CSS is generally recommended for designing large web pages?",
    answer: "C. External",
    options: [
      "A. Internal",
      "B. Inline",
      "C. External",
      "D. None of the Above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "How can we select an element with a specific ID in CSS?",
    answer: "B. #",
    options: ["A. @", "B. #", "C. .", "D. !"],
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "How can we select an element with a specific CLASS in CSS?",
    answer: "C. .",
    options: ["A. @", "B. #", "C. .", "D. !"],
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question:
      "Using Padding Of two values the description of the values are as follows respectively",
    answer: "C. Top&Bottom Left&Right",
    options: [
      "A. Left&Top Right&Bottom",
      "B. Top Bottom&Left",
      "C. Top&Bottom Left&Right",
      "D. None of the Above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question:
      "The CSS property used to specify the transparency of an element is?",
    answer: "B. Opacity",
    options: [
      "A. Filter",
      "B. Opacity",
      "C. Visibility",
      "D. None Of the Above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question:
      "How can we specify the spacing between each letter in a text in CSS?",
    answer: "C. letter-spacing",
    options: [
      "A. character-spacing",
      "B. word-spacing",
      "C. letter-spacing",
      "D. None of the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question:
      "Which of the following CSS property specifies the type of list item marker?",
    answer: "B. list-style-type",
    options: ["A. ul", "B. list-style-type", "C. ol", "D. list"],
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "What are the different types of gradients in CSS?",
    answer: "D. All Of The Above",
    options: [
      "A. linear-gradient",
      "B. Radial-gradient",
      "C. Conic-gradient",
      "D. All Of The Above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question:
      "Which of the following property specifies the look and design of an outline?",
    answer: "B. Outline",
    options: [
      "A. Outline-style",
      "B. Outline",
      "C. Design",
      "D. None Of The Above",
    ],
  },
];